Zaniness has no limits.
Animaniacs: Wakko's Wish is a animation, music,
comedy film directed by Liz Holzman.
The Warner Brothers (and the Warner Sister) go on a quest to find a
fallen wishing star to help Dot with her illness.
Unfortunately the rest of the town, including an evil king, also hear about the
star and want to get to it first to have their own wishes come true.
It's a race against time and it's up to the three
zany siblings to get there first.
Yakko Warner / Pinky / Dr. Otto Scratchansniff (voice), played by Rob Paulsen.
Wakko Warner (voice), played by Jess Harnell.
Dot Warner / Marita Hippo / Hello Nurse / Mindy's
Mother (voice), played by Tress MacNeille.
Brain / Squit (voice), played by Maurice LaMarche.
Mindy (voice), played by Nancy Cartwright.
Various (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Wakko's Wish (also known as Animaniacs: Wakko's Wish and originally titled as Wakko's Wakko Wish) is a 1999 American animated musical comedy-adventure fantasy
direct-to-video film based on the 1993–1998 animated series Animaniacs, and was the last work related to the series before the 2020 revival of the series.
It relocates all of the Animaniacs characters to a quasi-19th century fairy tale world and
portrays their race to find the wishing star that will grant them a wish.
The film was first released on VHS on December 21, 1999.
It contains 10 original songs and features a majority of the voice
cast reprising their respective roles from the TV show.
The film explores themes of woman director, sick relative, wishing on a star.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.